{
    "id": "fa592942ac594e12b19c25ffce64d40d",
    "title": "Adverbs Quiz",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "Although she works ……………………, she does not earn enough.",
            "description": "Hard is the adverb for this meaning. ",
            "answers": [
                "hard",
                "hardly"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "I am ……………………….. happy to hear this.",
            "description": "Very is used without much before adjectives. ",
            "answers": [
                "very",
                "very much",
                "too"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "It ………………………. rained this month.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "hardly",
                "rarely"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "I don’t want to go into …………………….. about how I managed to do this.",
            "description": "In detail means thoroughly or in depth.",
            "answers": [
                "detail",
                "details"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "Chennai can be ……………………… hot in May.",
            "description": "Either could be used here. Too can be used to show negative extremes. ",
            "answers": [
                "very",
                "too",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        },
        {
            "question": "A soldier should never behave ……………………..",
            "description": "Cowardly is an adjective. The adverb for this meaning is 'in a cowardly manner'. ",
            "answers": [
                "cowardly",
                "like a coward",
                "in a cowardly manner"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        },
        {
            "question": "I feel …………………………….. about his health.",
            "description": "Feel is a copular verb. It is modified by an adjective.",
            "answers": [
                "anxious",
                "anxiously"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "They were ……………………….. injured in the crash.",
            "description": "Badly and fatally are adverbs modifying verbs.",
            "answers": [
                "badly",
                "fatally",
                "deadly"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "I enjoy ………………………………. with my dogs.",
            "description": "Enjoy is followed by an ing form.",
            "answers": [
                "playing",
                "to play"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "Although she ran ………………………., she could not win the race.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "fast",
                "fastly"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "The movie was ………………………….. boring.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "rather",
                "quite",
                "too",
                "All of the above"
            ],
            "correct": 3
        },
        {
            "question": "Read the instructions …………………………..",
            "description": "Carefully is the adverb used to modify the verb read. ",
            "answers": [
                "careful",
                "carefully"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        }
    ]
}